vguard.in 2019-05-29

# V-Guard India | Privacy Policy

V-Guard Industries Ltd. believes strongly in protecting the privacy of the personally identifiable information shared with us through the use of this website. We believe it is important to inform you about how personal data obtained through this site will be used. We therefore encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully. 

Scope of this Privacy Policy  
This Privacy Policy applies to the personal information of visitors collected through this website by V-Guard Industries Ltd. and its subsidiaries. This includes all personal information collected online. 

The Information We Collect  
There are two forms of Information that V-Guard Industries Ltd. collects online: Website Visitor Information and Personally Identifiable Information voluntarily provided to V-Guard Industries Ltd. by visitors to the website. 

Website Visitor Information  
V-Guard Industries Ltd. gathers Information on Website activity, such as data on the number of people who visit the Website, the pages they visit, the duration of their stay, etc. This information is collected on an aggregate, anonymous basis, through web server logs and cookies, and will not contain Personally Identifiable Information. 

Personally Identifiable Information  
Personally Identifiable Information may be collected on certain pages of the Website. If you contact V-Guard Industries Ltd. online to ask a question, post a feedback, register a recently-purchased product, inquire about products you may already own, or participate in voluntary online surveys, the contact forms ask for certain types of Personally Identifiable Information to assist us in complying with your requests. This information is voluntarily given to V-Guard Industries Ltd. 

How We Use Information  
We use the information you provide about yourself to perform the service you have requested for. It may be used to provide you with information about other products of the company and promotions that may be of interest to you. The information may also be shared among our employees, agents or other related and unrelated entities and/or business partners acting on our behalf to conduct surveys or to provide a product or service you have requested. We do not share this information with other companies except to the extent necessary to complete your requests and, in the event we do share it, it is subject to their agreement to treat it as confidential business information and with the understanding that it may not be used for any purpose other than to perform their function. 

Safeguarding Information  
We recognize our responsibility to protect the information you entrust to us. V-Guard Industries Ltd. uses a variety of secure techniques to protect your information, including secure servers, firewalls, and encryption of financial data. 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, V-Guard Industries Ltd. has put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the Information we collect online.

The security of personal information you may submit in connection with a promotion entry, survey response, and/or registration for any feature on this Website is of the utmost concern to us, and we strive to ensure its security on our systems. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure, and hence we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you transmit such information at your own risk.

V-GUARD offers a range of products from Voltage Stabilizer to Digital UPS, Inverter and Inverter Batteries, Electric Water Heaters, Solar Water Heaters, Domestic Pumps, Agricultural Pumps, Industrial Motors, Domestic Switch Gears, Distribution Boards, Wiring Cables, Industrial Cables, Induction Cooktops, Mixer Grinders, Fans, Rice Cooker, Gas Stoves, Solar Power Systems & Air Coolers.
